Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Chicago Office. Information Center Records, 1901-2005 and undated RL.11121
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- 2018 Additions, 1901-2006 and undated; 1
  - Numbered Research Reports, 1919-1988 and undated; 10
    - X9.5-134-A. J. Walter Cooks, 1983 (Box R68)
    - X9.5-134.1-A. Michigan Lottery Study, 1983 (Box R68)
    - X9.5-137-A. Project Simon, 1984 (Box R68)
    - X9.5-138-A. Control Data Institute (CDI), 1984 (Box R68)
    - X9.5-139-A. Miller High Life and the U.S. Beer Industry, 1984; 2 folders (Box R68)
    - X9.5-140-A. Miller High Life Marketing Review, 1984 (Box R68)
    - X9.5-141-AB. Crackers Fact Sheet, 1984 (Box R68)
    - X9.5-142-A. California State Lottery Briefing, 1984 (Box R68)
  - Microfilmed Proofs and Research Reports, 1901-1969 and undated; 11
    - AD1. Earliest Ads; Alberto-Culver through Bauer & Black. 35mm microfilm, 1901-1968 (Box AV15)
      Includes Alberto-Culver (1963-1968); American Bakeries (1964-1966); American Trucking Association (1952-1954); Appliance Corporation of America (1947); Arnold Schwinn (1948-1953); Bauer & Black (1901-1917)
    - AD2. Bauer & Black through Better Homes & Gardens. 35mm microfilm, 1901-1961 (Box AV15)
      Includes Bauer & Black (1901-1943); Better Homes & Gardens (1956-1961)
    - AD3. Better Homes & Gardens through Blue Cross & Blue Shield. 35mm microfilm, 1920-1968 (Box AV15)
      Includes Better Homes & Gardens (1962-1968); Bishop & Babcock (1920-1923); Blue Cross & Blue Shield (1954-1956)
    - AD4. Blue Cross & Blue Shield through Bowman Dairy. 35mm microfilm, 1943-1965 (Box AV15)
      Includes Blue Cross & Blue Shield (1957-1965); Borg-Warner (1943-1959); Bowman Dairy (1934-1937)
    - AD5. Bowman Dairy. 35mm microfilm, 1938-1951 (Box AV15)
    - AD6. Bowman Dairy through Campbell-Taggart Bakeries. 35mm microfilm, 1926-1968 (Box AV15)
      Includes Bowman Dairies (1952-1962); A.S. Boyle (1916-1921); E.J. Brach (1949-1950); Brunswick (1940); Buckeye (1926); Burrus Mills (1937); William Campbell (1927-1928); Campbell-Taggart (1968)
    - AD7. Celotex Insulation through Chicago Milwaukee Railroad. 35mm microfilm, 1924-1962 (Box AV15)
      Includes Celotex (1924-1925); Central Manufacturing District (1959-1961; see also AD47); Central Public Service (1931); Central Wholesale Grocery (1934); Cheek-Neal Coffee (1927); Chicago Association of Commerce and Industry (1959-1962; see also AD47); Chicago Burlington & Quincy Railroad (1925-1929); Chicago Community Fund (1933-1937; see also AD47); Chicago Evening American (1933); Chicago Herald Examiner (1929); Chicago Milwaukee Railroad (1959-1960)
    - AD8. Chicago Milwaukee Railroad. 35mm microfilm, 1961-1966 (Box AV15)
    - AD9. Chicago Milwaukee Railroad through Cole Milling. 35mm microfilm, 1937-1968 (Box AV15)
      Includes Chicago Milwaukee Railroad (1967-1968); Chicago Tribune (1937-1948); Chun King (1954-1968); Chrysler (1943-1944); Clinton Corn (1959-1960); Cole Milling (1940-1947)
    - AD10. Continental Airlines. 35mm microfilm, 1958-1960 (Box AV15)
    - AD11. Continental Airlines through Coopers. 35mm microfilm, 1916-1963 (Box AV15)
      Includes Continental Airlines (1961-1963); Continental Motors (1916); Coopers (1939-1940)
    - AD12. Cream of Wheat. 35mm microfilm, 1922-1933 (Box AV15)
    - AD13. Cream of Wheat through Davey Tree Expert. 35mm microfilm, 1914-1957 (Box AV15)
      Includes Cream of Wheat (1934-1938); Credit Union (1952-1957); Crosley Radio (1929-1930); Crowell Publishing (1920-1927); Crown Jewel Ware (1948-1949); Curity & Castex (1939-1940); Curtiss Candy (1929); Danderine (1915-1932); Davey Tree Expert (1914-1919)
    - AD14. Davey Tree Expert through Elgin National Watch. 35mm microfilm, 1920-1968 (Box AV15)
      Includes Davey Tree Expert (1920-1936); Detroit Brewing (1937); Eisendrath Glove (1922-1923); Ekco Housewares (1967-1968); Elgin (1933-1943)
    - AD15. Elgin National Watch through Employers Mutuals of Wausau. 35mm microfilm, 1929-1965 (Box AV15)
      Includes Elgin (1944-1961); Emery Candles (1929); Employers Mutuals of Wausau (1953-1965)
    - AD16. Employers Mutual of Wausau through Ford Motor Company. 35mm microfilm, 1917-1968 (Box AV15)
      Includes Employers Mutual of Wausau (1965-1968); Felt & Tarrant (1917-1931); Ferro-Concrete (see AD17); First Federal Savings (1965-1968); Fleischmann (1924); Fleischmann Malting (1959-1965); Ford (1944-1946)
    - AD17. Ford Dealers Advertising Fund through Griesedieck Brewing. 35mm microfilm, 1914-1968 (Box AV15)
      Includes FDAF (1946-1968); Ferro-Concrete (1915-1916); Freeman Shoe (1961-1962); Geier (1921-1923); General Shoe (1939-1940); Gill Brothers (1914); Graham-Paige (1937-1939); Griesedieck Brewing (1936-1938)
    - AD18. Griesedieck Brewing through Hammond Organ. 35mm microfilm, 1917-1940 (Box AV15)
      Includes Griesedieck (1939-1940); Gruen Watch (1917-1932; see also AD19); Gulbransen Piano (1926-1927); Hammond Organ (1936-1937)
    - AD19. Hammond Organ through Illinois Power. 35mm microfilm, 1914-1968 (Box AV15)
      Includes Hammond (1938-1968); Harvey Federal Savings (1934); Hassler Manufacturing (1927-1929); Gruen Watch (1930-1932); Heisey's Glassware (1914-1920); Hellmann's Mayonnaise (1927-1929); Histon Products (1938); Hixson Products (1947); H.H. Hixson (1954-1956); Hoosier Manufacturing (1923-1927); Hooven & Allison (1920-1926); Horlick's Malted Milk (1915-1929); Illinois Power (1939-1940)
    - AD20. Illinois Power through Indiana Bell. 35mm microfilm, 1941-1961 (Box AV15)
      Includes Illinois Power (1941-1949); Indiana Bell (1948-1961)
    - AD21. Indiana Bell through Johnson Motors. 35mm microfilm, 1921-1968 (Box AV15)
      Includes Indiana Bell (1962-1968); Indiana Motor Truck Association (1953-1954); International Mineral & Chemical (1948-1950); International Packers (1961-1967); Iron Mountain (1927); Jackson Piano (1921-1922); Japan Tea Growers (1926-1929); Johnson Motors (1956-1964)
    - AD22. Johnson Motors through Kellogg. 35mm microfilm, 1915-1966 (Box AV15)
      Includes Johnson Motors (1965-1966); Outboard Marine International/Johnson-Evinrude (1964-1966); Robert A. Johnston (1956-1957); Julius Kayser (1915); Kellogg (1938-1941)
    - AD23. Kellogg through Kraft. 35mm microfilm, 1922-1946 (Box AV15)
      Includes Kellogg (1942-1943); Kent Products (1946); Klearflax (1922-1925); Kraft (1930-1931)
    - AD24. Kraft. 35mm microfilm, 1931-1934 (Box AV15)
    - AD25. Kraft. 35mm microfilm, 1935-1944 (Box AV15)
    - AD26. Kraft. 35mm microfilm, 1944-1949 (Box AV15)
    - AD27. Kraft. 35mm microfilm, 1949-1952 (Box AV15)
    - AD28. Kraft. 35mm microfilm, 1952-1956 (Box AV15)
    - AD29. Kraft Foods. 35mm microfilm, 1956-1959 (Box AV13)
    - AD30. Kraft Foods. 35mm microfilm, 1959-1963 (Box AV13)
    - AD31. Kraft Foods. 35mm microfilm, 1963-1966 (Box AV13)
    - AD32. Kraft Foods through Lewis-Howe. 35mm microfilm, 1916-1968 (Box AV13)
      Includes Kraft (1966-1968); Lever Brothers (1916-1950); Lewis-Howe (1941)
    - AD33. Libby McNeil & Libby. 35mm microfilm, 1912-1922 (Box AV13)
    - AD34. Libby McNeil & Libby. 35mm microfilm, 1922-1926 (Box AV13)
    - AD35. Libby McNeil & Libby. 35mm microfilm, 1927-1930 (Box AV13)
    - AD36. Libby McNeil & Libby. 35mm microfilm, 1931-1936 (Box AV13)
    - AD37. Libby McNeil & Libby. 35mm microfilm, 1937-1942 (Box AV13)
    - AD38. Libby McNeil & Libby. 35mm microfilm, 1943-1948 (Box AV13)
    - AD39. Libby McNeil & Libby. 35mm microfilm, 1948-1953 (Box AV13)
    - AD40. Libby McNeil & Libby. 35mm microfilm, 1953-1960 (Box AV13)
    - AD41. Libby McNeil & Libby through Lowrey Organ. 35mm microfilm, 1922-1968 (Box AV13)
      Includes Libby (1961-1968); Log Cabin (1922-1925); Lowrey (1959-1963)
    - AD42. Madison-Kipp through Oscar Mayer. 35mm microfilm, 1911-1968 (Box AV13)
      Includes Madison-Kipp (1921-1922); Maish, Chas. (1911); Marsh & McLennan (1968); Maxwell House (1925-1928); Oscar Mayer (1960-1962)
    - AD43. Oscar Mayer through Mobile Homes. 35mm microfilm, 1934-1968 (Box AV13)
      Includes Oscar Mayer (1963-1968); Mayonnaise Institute (1934); McGraw-Edison (1960-1963); Milk Mineral Co. (1937); Miller's National Federation (1947-1950); Mobile Homes (TCMA; 1950-1965)
    - AD44. Mobile Homes through Nash Motor. 35mm microfilm, 1915-1968 (Box AV13)
      Includes Mobile Homes (1966-1968); Moorman (1928-1930); Morris, Mann & Reilly (1922); Morten Milling (1936-1937); Morton International (1968); Morton's Salt (1940-1943); Mullens (1915); Murine (1956-1968); Mystic Adhesive (1953); Nash (1934-1935)
    - AD45. Nash Motor through Northern Trust. 35mm microfilm, 1927-1963 (Box AV13)
      Includes Nash (1936-1937); National Broadcasting Company (1944-1945); National Car Rental (1961-1963); National Dairy Products (1946-1948); Norge (1950-1954); Northern Pacific (1927); Northern Trust (1929-1933)
    - AD46. Northern Trust through Northwestern Mutual Life. 35mm microfilm, 1934-1955 (Box AV13)
      Includes Northern Trust (1934-1953); Northwestern Mutual (1948-1955)
    - AD47. Northwestern Mutual through Parker Pen. 35mm microfilm, 1913-1968 (Box AV13)
      Includes Northwestern Mutual (1956-1968); Odorono (1913-1925); Omar Bakeries (1937); Omar Mills (1937); Orange Crush (1933-1937); Chicago Community Fund (1933); Central Manufacturing District (1959-1961); Chicago Association for Commerce and Industry (1959-1961); Parker Pen (1942-1945)
    - AD48. Parker Pen through Pennsylvania Railroad. 35mm microfilm, 1924-1955 (Box AV13)
      Includes Parker Pen (1946-1955); Penick & Ford (1924); Pennsylvania Railroad (1926-1929)
    - AD49. Pennsylvania Railroad through Portland Cement. 35mm microfilm, 1914-1967 (Box AV13)
      Includes Pennsylvania Railroad (1930-1934); Perkins-Campbell (1914-1917); Pfeiffer Brewing (1965-1967); Pharma-Craft (1956-1959); Phoenix Hosiery (1922-1936); Pineapple Producers Association (1932-1934); Portland Cement (1957)
    - AD50. Portland Cement. 35mm microfilm, 1958-1960 (Box AV13)
    - AD51. Portland Cement. 35mm microfilm, 1960-1964 (Box AV13)
    - AD52. Portland Cement through Quaker Oats. 35mm microfilm, 1910-1968 (Box AV13)
      Includes Portland Cement (1965-1968); Postum Cereal (1924); Ferry Process Screws (1920); Printz Biederman (1921-1922); Procter & Gamble (1910-1911); Public Health Institute (1942-1946); Quaker Oats/Aunt Jemima (1917-1919)
    - AD53. Quaker Oats/Aunt Jemima. 35mm microfilm, 1919-1934 (Box AV13)
    - AD54. Quaker Oats. 35mm microfilm, 1953-1963 (Box AV13)
    - AD55. Quaker Oats through Rice Council. 35mm microfilm, 1914-1968 (Box AV13)
      Includes Quaker Oats (1963-1968); Lewis Manufacturing (1920); Rand McNally (1926-1934); Real Silk Hosiery (1928-1931); Realty Guarantee Trust (1914); Red Cross (1920-1921); Rice Industry (1959-1960); Rice Council (1961)
    - AD56. Rice Council through Schlitz. 35mm microfilm, 1915-1968 (Box AV13)
      Includes Rice Council (1962-1968); Richardson Roofing (1923-1926); Roddis Plywood (1957-1961); Quaker Oats/Muffets (1927-1928); Ronald Press (1915-1916); Savage Arms (1924); Schlitz (1956)
    - AD57. Schlitz through Schmidt. 35mm microfilm, 1957-1968 (Box AV13)
      Includes Schlitz (1957-1961); Schmidt Brewing (1966-1968)
    - AD58. Dr. Scholl's through Seven-Up. 35mm microfilm, 1911-1968 (Box AV13)
      Includes Dr. Scholl (1919-1924); Sealy (1958-1961); Sears Roebuck (1967-1968); Sechler (1916); Sentanel Remedies (1911); Seven-Up (1942-1944)
    - AD59. Seven-Up. 35mm microfilm, 1945-1955 (Box AV13)
    - AD60. Seven-Up through Shaw-Walker. 35mm microfilm, 1954-1968 (Box AV13)
      Includes Seven-Up (1956-1968); Shaw-Walker (1954-1964)
    - AD61. Shaw-Walker through Swift & Co.. 35mm microfilm, 1914-1968 (Box AV13)
      Includes Shaw-Walker (1965-1968); Shell Petroleum (1931); Shellmar Production (1949-1951); Simoniz (1967-1968); Sophie Mae Candy (1952-1958); Sta-Nu (1953-1954); Sterling Brewers (1962-1968); Storkline Furniture (1945-1950); S.W. Straus (1930); Successful Farming (1968); Superior Paper (1959-1960); Superior Underwear (1914-1915); Supervised Investors Service; Seven-Up (1968); Swift & Co. (1916-1922)
    - AD62. Swift & Co.. 35mm microfilm, 1922-1931 (Box AV13)
    - AD63. Swift & Co.. 35mm microfilm, 1931-1937 (Box AV13)
    - AD64. Swift & Co.. 35mm microfilm, 1937-1940 (Box AV13)
    - AD65. Swift & Co.. 35mm microfilm, 1933-1944 (Box AV13)
    - AD66. Swift & Co.. 35mm microfilm, 1944-1947 (Box AV13)
    - AD67. Swift & Co.. 35mm microfilm, 1948-1950 (Box AV13)
    - AD68. Swift & Co.. 35mm microfilm, 1951-1953 (Box AV13)
    - AD69. Swift & Co. through J. Walter Thompson. 35mm microfilm, 1943-1958 (Box AV13)
      Includes Swift (1954-1958); J. Walter Thompson (1943-1947)
    - AD70. J. Walter Thompson through Union Central Life Insurance. 35mm microfilm, 1911-1968 (Box AV13)
      Includes J. Walter Thompson (1948-1967); Toni (1945-1946); Trailways (1951-1967); Tromite (1924); Trus-Con Laboratory (pre-1916); Uncle Ben (1968); Union Central Life (1911-1934)
    - AD71. Union Central Life through Wadsworth Watch Case. 35mm microfilm, 1918-1960 (Box AV13)
      Includes Union Central Life (1935-1945); Union National Bank (1918); United Airlines (1934-1938); U.S. Yards and Transit (1959-1960); Vauv (1924); Wadsworth Watch Case (1919-1921)
    - AD72. Wadsworth Watch Case through Weco Products. 35mm microfilm, 1921-1955 (Box AV13)
      Includes Wadsworth Watch Case (1923-1934); War Savings Staff (1942-1943); Ward-Stillson (1921); Washington State Apples (1936); WBBM (1933); Webster Loose Leaf Filing (1922); Wells Organization (1954-1955); Weco (1926-1933)
    - AD73. Weco Products. 35mm microfilm, 1928-1937 (Box AV13)
    - AD74. Weco Products. 35mm microfilm, 1938-1959 (Box AV13)
    - AD75. Weco Products through Webb Young. 35mm microfilm, 1914-1967 (Box AV13)
      Includes Weco (1960-1962); Western Stationery (1922-1923); Weyerhaeuser (1930-1932); Wheatley Pottery (1914); Window Shade Institute (1942-1949); Wohl Shoe (1936); Woodbury/Andrew Jergens (1921-1929); Worcester Salt (1943); Wrigley (1931-1934); YMCA (1967); Yuban Coffee (1914-1921); Webb Young (1941)
    - AD76. Alberto Culver through Kraft. 35mm microfilm, 1960-1969 (Box AV13)
      Includes Alberto Culver (1969); Better Homes & Gardens (1969); Campbell Taggart Bakery (1969); Chicago Milwaukee Railroad (1969); Chicago Tribune (1969); Employers Insurance of Wausau (1969); Ford Dealers (1969); Hamm's Beer (1969); Hammond Organ (1969); Kraft Foods (1969); Kraft International (1960-1967)
    - AD77. Kraft International. 35mm microfilm, 1959-1968 (Box AV13)
    - AD78. Libby McNeil & Libby through YMCA. 35mm microfilm, 1962-1969 (Box AV13)
      Includes Libby (1969); March & McLennan (1969); Oscar Mayer (1969); Morton International (1969); Murine (1969); Northwestern Mutual (1969); Parker Pen (1969); Quaker Oats (1969); Rand-McNally (1962); Sears Roebuck (1969); Seven-Up (1969); Shaw-Walker (1969); Simoniz (1969); Successful Farming (1969); J. Walter Thompson (1969); Uncle Ben (1969); YMCA (1969)
    - RE1. T11.12-A11 through T21.4-C4.5. 16mm microfilm, undated (Box AV14)
      Includes reports on Swift
    - RE2. T21.4-C5 through T35.5-C2.3-vol.2. 16mm microfilm, undated (Box AV14)
      Includes reports on Borg-Warner, Weco, Pharmacraft
    - RE3. T35.5-C2.3-vol. 3 through T36.3-C39. 16mm microfilm, undated (Box AV14)
      Includes reports on Pharmacraft, Helene Curtis, Parker Pen
    - RE4. T36.3-C39.1 through T38.4-C11.1. 16mm microfilm, undated (Box AV14)
      Includes reports on Parker Pen, P. Ballantine and Sons, Schlitz
    - RE5. T38.4-C11.2 through T38.4-M4.1. 16mm microfilm, undated (Box AV14)
      Includes reports on Schlitz
    - RE6. T38.4-M8 through T38.8-C4. 16mm microfilm, undated (Box AV14)
      Includes reports on Schlitz, Sterling Co., Associated Brewing
    - RE7. T38.8 through T52.2-C2.1. 16mm microfilm, undated (Box AV14)
      Includes reports on Schmidt, Sears, Sealy Mattress, Lowrey Organ, Ekco, Johnson Co.
    - RE8. T52.2-C3 through T58.1-A.1. 16mm microfilm, undated (Box AV14)
      Includes reports on Northwestern Mutual, First Federal, Credit Union National Association, Blue Cross-Blue Shield
    - RE9. T58.1-A1 through T63-A10.4. 16mm microfilm, undated (Box AV14)
      Includes reports on Roddis Plywood, Portland Cement, Bowman, Kraft
    - RE10. T63-A11 through T63.1-M18.1. 16mm microfilm, undated (Box AV14)
      Includes reports on Kraft
    - RE11. T63.11-A1 through T63.3-A2.1. 16mm microfilm, undated (Box AV14)
    - RE13. T63.5-A.1 through T63.94-C4. 16mm microfilm, undated (Box AV14)
    - RE14. T63.94-C5 through T64-C25. 16mm microfilm, undated (Box AV14)
      Includes reports on Kraft, Libby
    - RE15. T64-C27 through T64.5-C10. 16mm microfilm, undated (Box AV14)
      Includes reports on Libby
    - RE16. T64.5-M4 through T65.44-A24. 16mm microfilm, undated (Box AV14)
      Includes reports on Libby, Swift
    - RE17. T65.44-A25 through T66-M1. 16mm microfilm, undated (Box AV14)
      Includes reports on Swift, Oscar Mayer
    - RE18. T66-M2 through T66.32-C1.4. 16mm microfilm, undated (Box AV14)
      Includes reports on Quaker Oats
    - RE19. T66.32-H1-vol.1 through T66.7-A8. 16mm microfilm, undated (Box AV14)
      Includes reports on Quaker Oats, Rice Council, American Bakeries
    - RE20. T66.7-C.1 through T67.7-C4. 16mm microfilm, undated (Box AV14)
      Includes reports on American Bakeries, Chun King
    - RE21. T67.7-C5 through T67.7-C69.2. 16mm microfilm, undated (Box AV14)
      Includes reports on Chun King
    - RE22. T67.7-C70 through T69.33-H1. 16mm microfilm, undated (Box AV14)
      Includes reports on Chun King, Brach, 7-Up; last report continued on RE23
    - RE23. T69.33-H1 through T71.63-H1a. 16mm microfilm, undated (Box AV14)
      Includes reports on 7-Up, Morton International, Continental Airlines
    - RE24. T71.63-M.1 through T83-A5. 16mm microfilm, undated (Box AV14)
      Includes reports on Continental Airlines, Trailways, Folding Paper Box Association of America, Wells Organization, Johnson Motors
    - RE25. T83-A5.1 through T83.1-M2. 16mm microfilm, undated (Box AV14)
      Includes reports on Johnson Motors
    - RE26. T83.1-M3 through T88-RT6. 16mm microfilm, undated (Box AV14)
      Includes reports on Outboard Motors, Elgin National Watch Company
    - RE27. T89.1-C1 through T95.1-M1. 16mm microfilm, undated (Box AV14)
      Includes reports on Sears, Roebuck & Co., National Restaurant Association
  - Audiovisual Materials, 1974-2005 and undated; 12
    - 2002 Let's Holiday (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-001)
    - Account Videos from World Partners Council Meeting 55:00, 1995 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-002)
      Includes Ford, DeBeers, Nestle, Kellogg, Kraft, Sprint
    - Agency Meeting/Holiday Party Reel, 2001 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-003)
    - Audio Studio presentation tape with 7-11 spot, undated (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-004)
    - Bars and 1kHz tone 20:00, undated (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-005)
    - Bars and 1kHz tone, undated (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-006)
    - Best of #2, 1990 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-007)
      Includes 7-Eleven, Brookfield Zoo, Gerber, Oscar Mayer, Quaker, Kellogg, Bristol Myers, Kraft, Northwestern Mutual Life, Sherwin Williams
    - Best of #4, 1991 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-008)
      Includes 7-Eleven, Lowenbrau, Quaker, Kraft, Sherwin Williams, Oscar Mayer, McDonnell Douglas, Premier Cruise Line, Brookfield Zoo, Life Source, Gerber
    - Bill Thompson, The Big Picture, 1995 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-009)
    - Brand Vision 22:00, 2000 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-010)
    - BrandZ, Comments from Malachy Walsh, Strategic Planning Director 3:00, 1999 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-011)
    - Butterfinger Crisp/Tollhouse compilation rough cuts, 2004 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-012)
      Includes Marriage Proposal, Press Conference
    - Butterfinger Historical Reel 1989-1997 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-013)
    - Capabilities presentation tape with presenters, 1993 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-014)
    - CEC Day One: Kids' Buying System, undated (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-015)
    - China: J. Walter Thompson and the People's Republic (John Mayer), 1985 (Box AV1, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-016)
    - Christmas Town Meeting video, 1994 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-017)
    - Christmas video master, undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-018)
    - Come Together, undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-019)
    - Consumer Immersions, undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-020)
      Includes Gerber: Project Marriott; Motorola Day One
    - Consumer insight presentation reel, 2000 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-021)
    - Corporate Sameness, undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-022)
    - Creative Planning Reel, 2000 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-023)
    - Creative Planning Reel, 2000 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-024)
      Includes Miller Genuine Draft, Miracle Whip, Blockbuster, Philly, Triscuit, Gap Heineken, First Union
    - Day One How To, undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-025)
    - Day One Seducing the Muse, 1995 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-026)
    - Eyes on Thompson: Bill Thompson "JWT a Worldwide Powerhouse", undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-027)
    - Eyes on Thompson: Bill Thompson "JWT a Worldwide Powerhouse", undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-028)
    - Eyes on Thompson: Chris Jones, Donald Kerr, JWT London, 1991 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-029)
    - Ford F-Series spots, 1997 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-030)
      Includes Launch, Canyon, Tough Is/3rd Door, Working Harder/Toughness
    - Fox Kids Network: Fox Kids, Rox Kids, undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-031)
    - Haagen-Dazs video :40 avid rough cut, 2003 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-032)
    - Holiday video print, undated (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-033)
    - Ivan Arthur presentation, James Webb Young Workshop (Hindustan Thompson), undated (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-034)
    - J. Walter Does That, 1997 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-035)
    - J. Walter Does That, 1996 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-036)
    - J. Walter Does That/Kids Version, 1997 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-037)
    - J. Walter Does That/Kids Version, 1995 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-038)
    - John Furr presentation, Asia/Pacific Managers Meeting, 1992 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-039)
    - John Furr remarks, Training Creative People, 1992 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-040)
    - JWT Chicago 100th Anniversary: 100 Years of Making Ads and Making History, 1991 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-041)
    - JWT Chicago 100th Anniversary: Coverage by Fox "9:30", 1991 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-042)
    - JWT Chicago 100th Anniversary: Videotaped anniversary greetings from JWT offices worldwide, 1991 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-043)
    - JWT Chicago 100th Anniversary: Worldwide Happy Birthday short and long versions, 1991 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-044)
    - JWT Chicago creative showcase reel, undated (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-045)
      Includes Miracle Whip, Oscar Mayer, PTA, Western Union, Wheat Thins, Salton, Nestle, Ritz Chips, Breakstone's, Butterfinger, Triscuit
    - JWT Summer Part SPF, 2002 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-046)
    - JWT Tweens Overview presentation reel, 1999 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11121-Umatic-047)